Guide to the University Photography records, [ca.1989-2001]
University Photography records,
- Faculty and staff
  - S-T
    - Talbot, Jan, 1993-1999 (Box 11, Folder 147)
    - Tallada, Bob, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 148)
    - Talluto, Eileen, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 149)
    - Tang, Chung, 1988-1993 (Box 11, Folder 150)
    - Tang, Jixin, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 151)
    - Tang, Martin, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 152)
    - Tanksley,Steve, 1993-2002 (Box 11, Folder 153)
      Copy of 2002 issue of Cornell Discoveries included. Negatives included as well
    - Tanner, Harold, 1999-2001 (Box 11, Folder 154)
      Negatives included, one set of photographs undated
    - Tappan, Linda, 1990-1995 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Tardos, Eva, 1992-2003 (Box 11, Folder 156)
    - Tatibouet, Cecily, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Tatkon, Carol, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Tauber, Loren, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Tauber, Maurice and Katherine, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 160)
      Photos of other staff included. One set of negatives and photographs undated
    - Taylor, Dean, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Tayne, Vajezatha, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Teitelblaum, Lee E., 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 163)
      Undated photograph and negative included
    - Telega, Lee, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 164)
    - Tennant, Priscilla, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 165)
    - Tennyson, Sharon, 1999-2001 (Box 11, Folder 166)
    - Terzian, Yervant, 1986-2002 (Box 11, Folder 167)
    - Teukolsky, Saul, 1991-2003 (Box 11, Folder 168)
    - Thannhauser, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 169)
      Negatives and last name only
    - Thevenin, Michelle, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 170)
    - Thiel, Pan, 1993-2001 (Box 11, Folder 171)
    - Thier, Sam, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 172)
    - Thomas, Gerry, 1994-1999 (Box 11, Folder 173)
    - Thomas, Marney, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Thomas, Sarah, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Thompson, Larry, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 176)
    - Thompson, Scott, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Thonney, Michael, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    - Thonney, Pat, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 179)
      One set of photographs undated
    - Thorbecke, Erik, 1996-2001 (Box 11, Folder 180)
      Dated and undated photocopies included
    - Thorne, Robert, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 181)
    - Tien, Norman, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 182)
    - Tierney, Brian, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 183)
    - Tigner, Maury, 1999-2001 (Box 11, Folder 184)
    - Tikefsky, Jeff, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 185)
    - Tillman, Ann, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 186)
    - Timmons, Michael, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 187)
    - Tiwari, Sandip, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 188)
    - Todd, Michael, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 189)
    - Togamivalie, Vasiti, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 190)
    - Tomek, William, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 191)
    - Tominey, Matt, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 192)
    - Tomsen, Jennifer, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 193)
    - Tonnizzi, C., 2003 (Box 11, Folder 194)
    - Topa, Mary, 1993-2001 (Box 11, Folder 195)
    - Topaloglu, Huseyin, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 196)
    - Topeleski, Leonard, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 197)
    - Torrence, Kenneth, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 198)
    - Torrey, Alicia, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 199)
    - Townsend, Alan, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 200)
    - Townsend, Bickley, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 201)
    - Tracey, John Bruce, 1993-2000 (Box 11, Folder 202)
    - Trautman, Charlie, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 203)
    - Travis, Susan, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 204)
    - Traynor, Jessica, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 205)
    - Tregurtha, Marci, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 206)
    - Tregurtha, Paul R., 1994 (Box 11, Folder 207)
    - Tricomi, Al, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 208)
    - Trinh, Kim-Chi, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Trochim, Bill, 1996-2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Trotter, Eric, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Truitt, Tracey, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Tseng, Yolanda, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Tufford, Peter, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Tun, San San, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Turcotte, Donald, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Turgeon, Gillian, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Turnbull, Deborah, 1986-2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Turner, Gloria, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Turner, James, 1969-2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      One negative undated
    - Turner, Janice, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Turner, Lowell, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Turner, Stephen, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Turner, Terry, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Tutu, Desmond, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Tyler, Lucia, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Tylutki, Tom, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - U-Z
    - Ugrin, Nicole, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Ulinski, Matt, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Unger, David, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Unrue, Kevin, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Usack, Ryszard, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Usher, David, 1970-2001 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Usner, Dan, 1991-1999 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      Negatives, undated photograph and photocopy included
    - Utter, Earl, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Valley, Kathleen, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Van Campden, Darryl, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Vandermark, Judy, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Van der Meulen, Marjolein, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Van Dover, Robert, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Van Dyk, Lewis, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Vanek, Jaroslav, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Vanes, Cindy, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Van Loan, Charles, 1998-2003 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Vanness, Linda, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Van Renesse, R., 2003 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - VanSickles, Kenny, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Vaughan, Stephanie, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Veeravalli, Venu, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Velasquez, Rhonda, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Veley, Mike, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Velez, Hector, 1994-2003 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Velleman, Paul, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      1999 article from Chronicle of Higher Education included. Negatives included
    - Venables, Bob, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Vennos, Debra, Undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Verdugo, Maria, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Viands, Paul, 1994-2003 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Vincent, Joe, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Viramontes, Helena Maria, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Vitullo, John, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Voelcher, Herb, 1990-1994 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Volma, Thomas, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Von Tiedmann, Andreas, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Votels, Verner, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Vussey, Galvin, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Wagner, John, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Wagner, Karen "Kay", 1993 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Wahlroos, Ingalill, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Walcott, Charles, 1986-1993 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Waldoff, Jessica, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Waldron, Anna, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      Negatives only. Descripton included
    - Waldron, Keith, 1994-2001 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Walker, Al, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Walker, Larry, 1988-2003 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Walkingstick, Kay, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Wallace, Don, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Walter, Robin, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Walters, Thomas W., 1996 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Wang, Jane, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Wang, Michelle, 1998-2003 (Box 12, Folder 72)
      Negatives only. Undated negatives included
    - Wang, Qi, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Wanno, Frank, Undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Wara, Bill, Undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Warbasse, Eric, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    - Ware, Barlow, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Warhaft, Zellman, 1994-2003 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Warkentin, Richard, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Warner, Richard, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Warren, Andy, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Warren, Beth, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Warren, Stanley, Undated (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Warsh, Molly, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Warzynski, Chester, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Wasserman, Ira, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 86)
    - Wasserman, Robert, 1968-2000 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Watanabe, Kazuo, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Waters, Jane, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Watkins, Christopher, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Watkins, Ramon, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Watkins, Sue, 1990-1995 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Wayno, Frank, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Weathers, Maura, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Webb, Watt, 1995-2003 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Webber, Mary, 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Wegman, William, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Weiler, Tom, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Weill, James, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Weill, Sandy, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Wein, Chris, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Weingarten, Helen, Undated (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Weingast, Barry, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Weinstein, Barry, 1992-1997 (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Weinstein, David, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Weinstein, Harel, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Weisner, Ulrich, 2001-2003 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Weiss, John, 1993-2003 (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Weiss, Roger J., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Weiss, Stephen H., 1997 (Box 12, Folder 110)
      Undated photograph and negatives included
    - Welbourne, Theresa, 1992-1999 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Welch, Ross and Combs, David, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Wells, Marty, 1991-2000 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Wells, Nancy, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Wessels, Anke, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - West, Beverly, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Wethington, Elaine, 1994-2003 (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Wettlauter, Scott, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Whalen, Charles, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Wheeler, Gene, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - White, Gail Scott, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - White, Jerry, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - White, Richard, 1988-1997 (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - Whiting, Ed, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - Whiting, Linda, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - Whitlock, Kathleen, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 126)
    - Wicker, Stephen, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - Widger, Bruce, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 128)
    - Wiedman, Martin, 1999-2002 (Box 12, Folder 129)
    - Wiesenfeld, John, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - Wilcox, Charles F., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 131)
    - Wilcox, Duane, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Wilken, Jeff, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 133)
    - Wilkens, Jennifer, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 134)
    - Wilkers, John, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Williams, Bob, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 136)
    - Williams, Chandra, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 137)
    - Williams, Damon, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 138)
    - Williams, Dennis, 1987-1995 (Box 12, Folder 139)
    - Williams, Karl, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Williams, Kim, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - Williams, Lynette Chapell, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - Williamson, Charles, 1995-2001 (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Wilson, Bob, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 144)
    - Wilson, James, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 145)
    - Winas, Stephen, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Winch, Dan, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Winkler, David, 1993-2002 (Box 12, Folder 148)
    - Winter, Alexander, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 149)
    - Wippmau, David, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 150)
    - Wise, David, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 151)
    - Wittink, Richard, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 152)
    - Wohlhueter, Dave, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 153)
    - Wolfe, David, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - Wolfner, Mariana, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 155)
    - Wolfram, Charles, 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 156)
    - Wolfson, Elissa, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 157)
    - Wolszczan, Alexander, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 158)
    - Wong, Wai-Kwong, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - Wood, Alan, 1989-2001 (Box 12, Folder 160)
    - Wood, Patricia, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 161)
    - Woodard, Sue, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 162)
    - Woods, David, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 163)
    - Wooley, Karen, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 164)
    - Worona, Steve, 1994-2000 (Box 12, Folder 165)
    - Wright, Ebnita, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - Wright, Michael, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - Wright, Patrick, 1999-2003 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - Wright, William, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 169)
    - Writer, Christina, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 170)
    - Wu, Ray, 1990-2000 (Box 12, Folder 171)
      Negatives and two undated photographs included
    - Wyatt, David, 1970-1994 (Box 12, Folder 172)
    - Xu, Chunhui (Chris), 2002 (Box 12, Folder 173)
    - Yanai, Ruth, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 174)
    - Yang, Xiangzhong, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 175)
    - Yeh, David, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 176)
    - Yen, Andrew, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 177)
    - Yona, Golan, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 178)
    - Young, Martie, 1972-1998 (Box 12, Folder 179)
    - Young, Ruth, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 180)
    - Youst, William, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 181)
    - Yun, Joseph, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 182)
    - Zaitland, Milton, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 183)
    - Zaslow, Neal, 1979-1998 (Box 12, Folder 184)
    - Zehnder, Alan, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 185)
    - Zhang, Rachel, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 186)
      Negatives and one photocopy only
    - Zhong, Huan, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 187)
    - Ziegler, Jerome, 1983-1993 (Box 12, Folder 188)
      Undated photographs included
    - Zinder, Stephen, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 189)
    - Zorn, Peter, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 190)
    - Zumoff, Joel, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 191)
    - Unidentified (Box 12, Folder 192)